## **Dmitrii** Lisin

mrlisdim@gmail.com 8 (999) 529-5331

Since childhood, I've been in love with programming. When I began my career as an intern at an electronics design firm, I discovered that I enjoyed creating something that worked in real life rather than just inside my computer. I have finished a lot of embedded projects from different spheres and dealt with numerous instruments, protocols, and peripherals. It has always been my intention to write only high-quality, human-readable code. Had prior team leadership experience, but preferred to work as an equal member of the team. In my free time, I also prefer to extend my knowledge of programming languages, techniques, and trends by working with hobby projects.

Twitter mrlisdim Github mrdimfox Telegram @mrlisdim LinkedIn dmitrii-lisin

#### **SKILLS**

EMBEDDED DEVELOPMENT	C/C++, Zephyr, FreeRTOS, STM32, Nordic, Real-time protocols, Industrial protocols, Stack only programming
PYTHON DEVELOPMENT	FastAPI, Pydantic, ORM, WAMP protocol, Async, Threading
CI/CD	Docker, Docker Compose, Github Actions, Gitlab Pipelines
WEB DEVELOPMENT	HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Typescript, React, Parcel, Rollup
RUST	Tauri
COMMON	VSC, Gitlab, Github, Reviewing, Linux, Reading schematics, Datasheet exploring

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Team leader Jan 2020 - Present

Developed a flexible testing system for embedded electronics based on distributed micro-services connected by PubSub/RPC Web-protocol.

- Robster: flexible testing system for electronic devices (Python, WAMP, Microservice, Docker, PostgreSQL)
- Gate valve controller (ARM, STM32, Zephyr, Modbus)
- GPS tracker for a professional training (ARM, Nordic, GPS, UBlox, Ant)

Embedded Software Developer Jan 2013 - Jan 2020

Have been finished more than 20 commercial projects in embedded area including IoT, safety systems, shipbuilding.

- Pastilda: hardware password manager (STM32, ARM, Crypto Peripheral, SDIO, FatFS, FreeRTOS)
- Ship ruder control system (ARM, STM32, USB HID, FreeRTOS)
- Fire alarm system (ARM, STM32)
- MTUTA: Telemetry of vending machines (ARM, FreeRTOS, USB, SD, SIMCom, GSM, Ethernet, FTP)

#### **EDUCATION**

# **ITMO University**

Jan 2016 - Jan 2018

Master - Intelligent Technologies in Robotics

#### **ITMO University**

Jan 2012 - Jan 2016

Bachelor - Intelligent Technologies in Robotics

### **LANGUAGES**

English *Fluent* 

INTERESTS	
Games	
Books	
Traveling	
Hobby programming	
REFERENCES	

Russian *Native Speaker* 

— Ivan Larionov, LLC "Third Pin" CEO